debtsolver.co.uk 2013-02-01

# Debtsolver Privacy Policy

This website is brought to you by Debt Solver Ltd. We take the privacy of our website users very seriously. We ask that you read this Privacy Policy ('the Policy') carefully as it contains important information about how we will use your personal data.

For the purposes of the Data Protection Act 1998, Debt Solver Ltd ('we' or 'us') is the 'data controller' (i.e. the company who is responsible for, and controls the processing of, your personal data).

**Personal data we may collect about you**

We will obtain personal data about you (such as your name and address) whenever you complete an online enquiry.

We may monitor your usage of this website. This may include monitoring how many times you visit, which pages you go to, traffic data, location data and the originating domain name of a user's internet service provider. This information helps us to build a profile of our users. Some of this data will be aggregated or statistical, which means that we will not be able to identify you individually. Please see further the section on 'Use of cookies' below. Occasionally we may receive information about you from other sources which we will add to the information which we already hold about you in order to help us improve and personalise our service to you.

**How we may use your personal data**

We will use your personal data for the purposes described in the data protection notice that was given to you at the time your data were obtained. These purposes include:

  * To help us identify you
  * Administration 
  * Statistical analysis 
  * Customer profiling and analysing your purchasing preferences
  * Marketing — see 'Marketing and opting out' below
  * Fraud prevention and detection
  * Customising this website and its content to your particular preferences
  * To notify you any changes to this website or our services which may affect you
  * Improving our products and services

**Marketing and opting out**

We may share your personal data with organisations who are our business partners and we or they may contact you, unless you have asked us or them not to do so, by email, telephone, fax or mail about our products, special offers or other information which may be of interest to you from time to time. If you prefer not to receive any further marketing communications from us, you can opt out at any time. See further 'Your rights' below.

**Disclosure of your personal data**

We may disclose your personal data to:

  * other companies within our group
  * our agents and service providers (e.g. providers of web hosting or maintenance services)
  * law enforcement agencies in connection with any investigation to help prevent unlawful activity
  * our business partners in accordance with the 'Marketing and opting out' section above.

**Keeping your data secure**

We will use technical and organisational measures to safeguard your personal data, for example:

  * we store your personal data on secure servers 

Whilst we will use all reasonable efforts to safeguard your personal data, you acknowledge that the use of the internet is not entirely secure and for this reason we cannot guarantee the security or integrity of any personal data which are transferred from you or to you via the internet.

**Monitoring**

We may monitor and record communications with you (such as telephone conversations and emails) for the purpose of quality assurance, training, fraud prevention and compliance.

**Information about other individuals**

If you give us information on behalf of someone else, you confirm that the other person has appointed you to act on his/her behalf and has agreed that you can:

  * give consent on his/her behalf to the processing of his or her personal data  

  * receive on his/her behalf any data protection notices

**Use of cookies**

When you use this website, we may collect information about your computer, such as your IP address and/or browser, which we will use for administration purposes and statistical analysis. This information will not usually identify you personally.

We may also obtain information about your online movements and use of the internet. We do this by placing a 'cookie', which is a small file, on your computer's hard disk. Cookies are used for several reasons:

  * to recognise you whenever you visit this website  

  * to speed up access to this website (so you do not have to log on each time)
  * to store your personal preferences
  * to build a profile about you
  * to better target our marketing and advertising campaigns
  * to identify which web pages are being used

The vast majority of web browsers accept cookies. However, you can change your browser settings so that cookies are not accepted. If you do this, you may lose some of the functionality of this website. For further information about cookies and how to disable them please go to: aboutcookies.org

**Transfers of data out of the EEA**

We may need to transfer your personal data to certain countries which are located outside the European Economic Area. Any transfer of your data will be subject to a European Commission approved contract which will safeguard your privacy rights and give you remedies in the unlikely event of a security breach.

**Your rights**

You have the right, subject to the payment of a small fee (currently £10) to request access to personal data which we may process about you. If you wish to exercise this right you should:

  * put your request in writing
  * include proof of your identity and address (e.g. a copy of your driving licence or passport, and a recent utility or credit card bill)  

  * attach a cheque in the amount of £10 made payable to Debt Solver Limited  

  * specify the personal data you want access to, including any account or reference numbers where applicable.  

You have the right to require us to correct any inaccuracies in your data free of charge. If you wish to exercise this right you should:

  * put your request in writing
  * provide us with enough information to identify you (e.g. account number, username, registration details)   

  * specify the information that is incorrect and what it should be replaced with.  

You also have the right to ask us to stop processing your personal data for direct marketing purposes. If you wish to exercise this right you should:

  * put your request in writing (an email sent to [info@debtsolver.co.uk](mailto:info@debtsolver.co.uk) with a header that says 'Unsubscribe' is acceptable)  

  * provide us with enough information to identify you (e.g. account number, username, registration details)  

  * if your objection is not to direct marketing in general, but to direct marketing by a particular channel (e.g. email or telephone) please specify the channel you are objecting to.  

**Our contact details**

We welcome your feedback and questions. If you wish to contact us, please send an email to [info@debtsolver.co.uk](mailto:info@debtsolver.co.uk) or you can write to us at Debt Solver Limited, Trafford Plaza, 73 Seymour Grove, Manchester M16 0LD. 

We may change this privacy policy from time to time. You should check this policy occasionally to ensure you are aware of the most recent version which will apply each time you access this website.
